There's nothing Yoshikage Kira
despises more…
than being the center of attention.
To suffer such a sickening humiliation
in front of complete strangers…
How could myself-piloting
Heart Attack be ensnared…
Shit… I have to reverse
this witchcraft fast…
Hey there, buddy. You okay?
Not feeling too good?
Want me to call your mommy?
I'm doing fine. Now beat it.
Hey, hey, hey, did you hear that?
Is all that booze making you
dream pretty little dreams
in that head of yours?
Having fun? Enjoying the buzz?
GRASP
Nice suit you got there.
You know, we just got fired
and are flat broke.
The ladies aren't exactly
lining up either.
So when I see guys like you,
I get a little agitated.
Come on, don't just lie there.
Hey, buddy.
Your shoelaces are untied.
I'll tie them for you.
A nice big ol' knot!
Now that's thoughtful!
H-Hey, what's wrong?
That's Deadly Queen's
Bomb Type One.
It turns anything it touches
into a bomb.
Th-The doctor! Call the doctor!
- Today's been a disaster.
- Get me a doctor!
All Yoshikage Kira
wants is a quiet life…
and then those pieces of shit
had to interfere…
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
EPISODE 24
HEART ATTACK, PART 2
Hey, Josuke.
What the hell happened
at that shoe shop?
Got me, but whatever it was,
it wasn't good.
Hurry! It'll take about
five minutes to get there.
It looks cracked.
That must mean
that bomb Stand's user is hurt too.
Please do not venture too far
from my side.
My range is five meters.
Act 3's is five meters.
It is a fact that we have matured.
Our power is even greater
than before.
My inferior range
in comparison with Act 2
is an unavoidable shortcoming.
GRAVITY
Moving outside my five-meter range
removes the weight
applied to the target object,
in effect exciting it
to even greater heights,
and inciting it to rush toward us
like an animal in heat.
Conversely, moving closer
to the target object
GRAVITY
increases the force applied to it.
What would you like to do?
N-Nothing… I want him right there.
I hope Josuke gets here soon.
I hear a new gym is about to open
near Budogaoka High School.
I'm seriously considering joining.
I should probably
build up my strength.
Then again, I could very well
end up lifting the same dumbbells
or swimming in the same pool
as guys who've been busier
playing with their dicks
than bathing.
It took me three minutes
to get here.
I realized the full extent
of my weakness
when I tried to cross
at the crosswalk.
By the way, who else
will be joining us today?
You called on someone for help,
didn't you?
Josuke Higashikata and
Okuyasu Nijimura live the closest.
That's about five minutes away,
so I suppose they have
two minutes to go?
- You're their friend, aren't you?
- Y-You…
Yukako Yamagishi and that woman who
runs Beauty Institute Cinderella
are so-called Stand users
as well, correct?
You wouldn't cry to her for help,
now, would you?
Y-You're…
I left my jacket
with the button behind.
I shall retrieve it later…
After I do away with you.
It's him… right before my eyes!
This is the man…
Year after year,
victim after victim…
Reimi, Shigechi…
Make him suffer, Act 3!
DOGYUUN
Deadly Queen!
Why does he have two Stands?
A person is supposed to have
only one Stand!
Heart Attack is a smart bomb,
which I launch from
Deadly Queen's left hand.
That's why the damage
is confined to my left hand.
Take heed, Master Koichi.
You have just left
the five-meter range.
The force suppressing
his bomb Stand will dissipate.
S-h-i-t.
I must initiate 3 Freeze again.
Fascinating… So it has a range…
To whom shall I direct my attack?
The actual murderer,
or that piece-of-shit bomb Stand?
3 Freeze cannot weigh down
two targets at once.
Even if we immobilize the user,
the bomb Stand will
keep charging on auto-pilot.
If we immobilize the bomb,
the user will rush in for the kill.
Which will it be?
Your orders, please.
To whom shall I direct my attack?
S-Stop the bomb!
3 Freeze!
KER-BAM-BAM
It appears you were
destined for defeat,
irrespective of
your target of attack.
I used to think Heart Attack
was invincible.
To think it would be rendered
completely ineffective…
First I had to compensate
the café for its losses,
then there was the confrontation
with those hooligans.
I feel like I've been
taken for a ride.
This is a major first.
Never have I ever been
so challenged.
I'm even left with
this slight taste of defeat.
My deepest respects.
You are something else… boy.
By the way, you wouldn't happen
to have any tissues, would you?
Or a handkerchief is fine.
Hm? I paid you my respects.
You could at least
converse with me.
I have… none.
Then use mine.
Your nose is gushing blood,
isn't it?
I offered so you could
clean yourself up.
I'm about to end your life
by mauling.
I have a little over a minute
before your friends get here.
Leaving you alive
just doesn't sit right with me.
Especially after
that public humiliation.
Hey, hey, you can stop
that ridiculous groaning now.
I endured the same pain
you feel now
through recent events,
but I didn't complain.
You sure you are a boy?
You should learn by my example.
See? Tissues come in hand,
don't they?
I'll dab the blood for you.
They say a stuffed up nose
leads to slowed cognition.
You know, not long ago,
I was groveling on the floor
just like you.
In one minute, I will vaporize you
with Deadly Queen.
Until that moment, I suggest
you learn from yours truly
and take the pain.
Learn to be tough
in the face of resistance!
Y-Your name…
is Yoshikage Kira…
Yoshikage Kira is your real name…
My driver's license!
When did you swipe my wallet?
You little pathetic turd…
You said you had to
reimburse the café, right?
That's when it hit me.
What does that have to do
with anything?
What good does it do you
to know my name?
In a matter of moments,
you will cease to exist.
Yeah, I know you're
about to kill me.
But even I was able to
figure out your name.
You're not so tough.
You might get away for now,
but I wonder what you're thinking?
A little pathetic turd just
unravelled the mystery of your name
without breaking a sweat.
I'll say it again.
A little pathetic turd
just found you out!
You're the biggest dumb ass
I've ever seen!
I'll be waiting for you
on the other side, son of a bitch!
You bastard!
Damn it! Why do I feel like
the one who's lost?!
REVERB ACT 3
KOICHI HIROSE
Infuriating brat.
I still have a minute before
Josuke and Okuyasu show up.
And here I thought roughing him up
would settle my spirit.
He's got his socks on inside-out.
I suppose it doesn't bother him…
That's it, I can't stand it!
Not that way, Okuyasu!
But Centipede Shoes is this way.
If we go this way, we'll get there
in a minute! Hurry up!
Put them on right.
That gnawing unease is gone.
And now I can scatter
your atoms like dust!
Deadly Queen!
The tip of this finger can
transform any object into a bomb.
I suppose, in your case,
it will be your student badge.
Bomb Type One!
Koichi, your spirit has prevailed.
What?!
Well, what a surprise.
I wouldn't have guessed
you'd be able to
prop yourself up
with those injuries…
You would've been much better off
entering
your eternal slumber there.
In fact, I think I can see
the trees behind you
through those gapping wounds.
Nice watch you got there.
Take one last look cause
I'm gonna bust it up real good…
By it I mean your face.
You certainly are
an intriguing individual.
I'd love to learn your name,
among other things,
but I really must mosey on
to my next destination.
I have a mere twenty seconds left.
Mindless small talk
just isn't on the agenda.
Your Stand just now
was surprisingly feeble.
Like catching a simple pop fly.
Do you really think your frailty
can overcome Deadly Queen's power?
SMASH
Wh—
S-Such speed…
How can you move so fast?
Now that I got a closer look…
Good grief, that's a tacky watch.
Though, that's the least
of your worries now…
I can think of something
that's gonna look a lot worse…
and that something is your face.
What is this Stand?
It's so fast… like it stopped time!
Koichi, if it weren't for you,
I would have been long dead.
You fought valiantly, without
anyone to help you by your side.
You deserve great respect, Koichi.
You've matured.
Hey, Koichi!
Koichi!
W-What the heck happened?
K-Koichi! Jotaro!
Be on the lookout, Okuyasu.
What in the hell happened?!
Jotaro! Koichi!
Calm down. I have to
find out if Koichi is still alive.
If he is, I can heal him
with Shining Diamond.
Yes! Jotaro's alive!
But just barely.
K-Koichi is too.
But he's not breathing!
Hurry! Hurry and heal him, Josuke!
Hey, he's not waking up!
- I can't believe it…
- But he should be healed.
- Josuke and Okuyasu are here.
- He's hurt bad!
It's gonna take him a while
to come to.
Today has been utter hell…
Never have I lived through
such a horrible day.
Yoshikage Kira has always
been able to overcome anything…
I'll get out of this… I will.
What are you doing?
Hey, he's awake.
Hey, don't try anything funny.
Turn around very slowly.
Show us your face!
Be careful!
Stay away from Centipede Shoes!
Some crazy explosion
is about to go off!
The owner was
blown into the street!
Those two were too!
An explosion?
H-Hey, calm down.
Were you caught in the blast?
I'm just an office worker.
But I'm not gonna make it…
I'm losing too much blood.
I-It hurts!
H-Hey, calm down.
It's gonna be all right.
I can heal you.
Where does it hurt?
I think one of my ribs
might have punctured my lung.
H-Hurry, save me, please!
Hurry?
Oh? Last I checked, I looked like
I was still just in high school,
so why would you ask me
to treat your wounds?
I have trouble getting into
pachinko parlors,
and I look like some
med-school graduate to you?
You totally took the bait.
You saw my Shining Diamond,
didn't you?
Crap… I got too excited
Which means you're the enemy.
What we've got here
is a double knockout.
Th-This guy's the murderer?!
I guess this means I've lost.
You're right, I'm the one
you've been looking for.
You know my identity,
the true nature of my Stand,
you even know my real name.
I guess sleeping like a baby
isn't really in the cards…
I mean, of course, for tonight!
Deadly Queen!
What the hell are you doing?!
Exactly what it looks like.
I severed my own hand.
I-It hurts… It hurts so bad,
so much blood.
Look at me, I'm crying.
To me, victory and defeat
means nothing.
I assure you I will survive.
I will live on
in peaceful tranquility.
I have to live with
the insatiable desire to kill,
but I promise you,
I will live happily ever after!
Heart Attack, you are free!
I leave the rest to you.
Your duty is to protect me.
Well look at
this cute little plaything…
Josuke, that's a bomb Stand,
and it goes after thermal energy!
It's completely indestructible!
Your body temperature
will set it off!
So you can't bust it to pieces?
Bust it to pieces?
Quite the contrary. I fixed it.
With his hand left behind…
It's not the prettiest sight
to look at,
but the hand is leading us
to our murderer.
Let's go!
Yeah!
You're not getting away
that easily, freakin' crackpot!
H-Hey, look over there…
I will sleep peacefully again…
K-Kira? Why is your face
caked in blood?
Hey, guys.
Time to head home already?
I'm in a hurry, later then.
The murderer's name is
Yoshikage Kira.
His address is
Morioh Kotodai 1 -128.
He's 33 years old.
He wields a short-range bomb Stand,
Deadly Queen!
Hey, where is this guy running to?
It doesn't matter where. He's dead!
He's in this building.
Hey, wait… This is…
Beauty Institute Cinderella!
What's he doing here?!
A-Aya! Are you there?
Dr. Aya Tsuji!
A-Aya's…
Aya's…
What is this?
What the hell happened?!
He's dead…
Why is Yoshikage Kira dead?
Aya!
Th-This is…
What the hell happened?
Wait!
That man isn't Yoshikage Kira!
He has his left hand!
Huh?
His face is missing!
What?!
He's missing his fingerprints
on his right hand, too.
Who is this guy?
That man…
That man has
the same height and build…
That man was brought here by him,
he killed him right before my eyes.
He's too terrible for words…
He made me use Cinderella
to replace his face.
And his hair and fingerprints…
So he's someone else now?
Yes…
H-His face…
Shining Diamond!
H-His…
Josuke, don't touch her! Get away!
His face…
Aya!
On the other side of that door!
You're not getting away, damn it!
Th-This is…
I-It's the commute home…
There's so many people…
W-Which one is he?
Which one is Yoshikage Kira?!
Yoshikage Kira, you gutless prick!
Get out here!
He managed to get away.
He won't be afraid,
and he won't be hiding.
You can bet he will stay
right here in Morioh.
He'll go on living
as he always has.
AYA TSUJI: DECEASED
YOSHIKAGE KIRA'S METAMORPHOSIS,
A NEW FACE, A NEW NAME,
A NEW ADDRESS
Aya Tsuji: deceased
Yoshikage Kira's metamorphosis,
a new face, a new name,
a new address
EPISODE 25
HEART FATHER